Hey this thief clearly didn't do his homework on the place he
Привет этот Воришка явно не изучал место
was about to rob there
которое собрался грабить
comes a time in every parent's life
у каждого родителя наступает момент
when the kid brings home a
когда ребнок приводит домой своего
weird
странного
friend wow bey
друга Вау
y
Бей й
[music]
[музыка]
[applause]
[аплодисменты]
it looks like this storm is almost moving du north so it's going to move probably right up saine river that's not
it looks like this Storm is almost
good we're going to be out the
River That's not good we're going to be
way
out the way
по
по
[music]
[музыка]
undercurrents are one of those
подводные течения - это одна из тех
things divers have to deal with on a regular basis
вещей с которой дайверам регулярно
[music]
[музыка]
deal that's what a really high-
дело вот что такое по-настоящему
speed train is
скоростной поезд
L
L
por
por
exemplo Po lavine lavine
exemplo Po lavine lavine
sometimes the neighbors come over with weird
бывает что соседи приходят Со странными
claims but this old man has taken it to a
претензиями но этот старик вышел на
new level
новый уровень
I've been here two years I've happily used the wifi and uh now I see
I've been Here Two years I've happily
that you
used The WiFi and uh Now I See that you
you put a password on it and I can't use it
you Put A Password on it And I Can't use
I think being
it I think being
unreasonable Okay [
unreasonable Okay
music]
[музыка]
po [
ро
po
по
maho beach on the island of San Martin one of the
пляж махо на острове Сан Мартен одна из
most unique places in the world where
самых уникальных мест в мире где
planes fly literally
самолёты пролетают буквально в
a few meters above the heads of
нескольких метрах Над головами
vacationers this elephant comes here not for the
отдыхающих этот слон приходит сюда не в
first time to steal the remains of food but
первый раз чтобы стащить остатки еды но
this time he was caught red-handed
в этот раз он был пойман с поличным
robby go away
robby go away
[music]
[музыка]
Vi
Vi
Ja
Ja
[music] it
[музыка]
was a day off but the girl still really
был выходной но Девочка всё равно очень
wanted to go to school
хотела поехать в школу
sometimes we just find ourselves at the wrong
иногда мы просто оказываемся не в то
time and in the wrong place
время и не в том месте
couriers often get it
курьерам нередко приходит
from dogs but this big guy faced
от собак но этот здоровяк столкнулся с
something more complicated
чем-то посложнее
[music]
[музыка]
wanted to capture the local beauty but
хотел заснять местные красоты но
accidentally ended up on someone else's territory
случайно попал на чужую территорию
[music]
[музыка]
W
W
summer of
летом
2023 torrential rains led to
2023 года проливные дожди привели к
severe floods in India and rivers overflowed their
сильным наводнениям в Индии и реки вышли
banks the destructive elements did not
из берегов разрушительная стихия не
spare even
пощадила даже
buildings This is what
зда Так выглядит дозаправка
supersonic aircraft refueling in the air looks like
сверхзвуковых самолётов в воздухе
2 3
2 3
[music]
[музыка]
Oh
Oh
in 2024 floods turned
в 2024 году наводнение превратили
some roads in New Mexico into
некоторые дороги в штате нью-мексико в
Stormy
Бурные
rivers a
реки а
K
K
Having such a sharp nose, the sailfish
Имея такой острый нос рыба парусник ещё
can also keep up with a motorboat you ca
и может угнаться за моторной лодкой с
n't joke with it
ней шутить не
[music]
[музыка]
standing a
стоит а
C
C
[music]
[музыка]
Sorry but someone has to stay behind
Извини но кто-то должен остаться в
as a guard
качестве охранника
[music]
[музыка]
yeah
да
those rings of bubbles mean
такие кольца из пузырьков воды означают
humpback whales hunt schools of fish in this area
что в этом месте горбатые киты охотятся
[music]
[музыка]
Mudflow - It's just a mixture of water and
Сель - Это всего лишь смесь воды и
rock but its destructive power Is
горных пород но его разрушительная сила
impressive
Впечатляет
[applause]
[аплодисменты]
Mercedes
Mercedes
black wait
чёрный подожди
irrefutable proof that
неопровержимое доказательство того что
cats are liquid
коты - это жидкость
[music]
[музыка]
that time when a friend asked
тот самый случай когда друг попросил
you to wake him up
тебя разбудить его
ah
ah
oh
о
[laughter]
[смех]
few situations can top
мало какой ситуации удастся переплюнуть
this one for awkwardness
эту по неловкости
On
On
[applause]
[аплодисменты]
A
A
[music]
[музыка]
hur ST D hur ST
hur ST D hur ST
Right Oh
Right Oh
[music]
[музыка]
my wicky
my wicky
[applause]
[аплодисменты]
3 Two
3 Two
[music]
[музыка]
?
?
poor guy decided to take revenge for
Бедняга решил отомстить за
everyone Oh
всех Oh
You've probably seen how crowds of people
Ты наверняка видел как толпы людей
make waves in stadiums But in a
пускают волну на стадионах А вот в
Korean swimming pool they make a real
корейском бассейне делают настоящую
wave out of
волну из
people what you see are
людей то что ты видишь рации
coordinated walkie-talkies the flight of a huge
скоординированные полёт огромного
number of birds
множества птиц
[music]
[музыка]
know
know
[applause] [
[аплодисменты]
music]
[музыка]
in their lives these chimpanzees have never seen
в своей жизни эти шимпанзе не видели
anything but laboratory walls But here's a
ничего кроме лабораторных стен Но вот
touching moment when they are released into freedom for the first time
трогательный момент когда их впервые
a friend wanted to admire the power of the
приятель хотел полюбоваться мощностью
waves up close but they quickly discouraged this
волн вблизи но они быстро отбили это
desire
желание
[music]
[музыка]
The Oh My
The Oh My
God is Gone so
God is Gone
sorry
so sorry
H
H
[music]
[музыка]
in case If you were wondering Where does
на случай Если тебе было интересно Куда
paper from public
пропадает бумага из обществен х
[music]
[музыка]
cat's cleaning
убор кота
this terrifying natural phenomenon
это устрашающее природное явление
is called a thunderstorm collar such
называют грозовым воротником такие
clouds form on the border of atmospheric
облака образуются на границе атмосферных
fronts
фронтов
[music]
[музыка]
that oh How Cool Is that though the way
that oh How Cool Is that though the way
is Rolling
is Rolling
[music] [
[музыка]
working  calmly carried out his tasks
рабочий спокойно выполнял свои задачи
when he suddenly discovered that he had caused a
как вдруг обнаружил что он стал причиной
local resident to move
переезда местного жителя
[music]
[музыка]
I think She Might be What are you doing Oh Mama Get your baby ahead Mama Go On
I think She Might
Get your baby the
baby ahead Mama Go On Get your baby
author of the video had no idea who was
автор видео понятия не имела кто
leaving food outside her door until she
оставляет ей под дверью еду пока не
installed a peephole with a camera She decided to
установила глазок с камерой Она решила
pay her back in kind [music
отплатить ей тем же
]
[музыка]
S
S
go to you
иди у тебя
[music] a
[музыка]
child
ребёнок
for x fifth fortress But not for this
длях пя крепость Но не для этого
[music]
[музыка]
beagle there are beauties that are best
бигля есть красоты которыми лучше
admired from afar
любоваться издалека
[music]
[музыка]
jy jy jy jy
jy
[
[музыка]
use
use
[music]
[музыка]
K
K
S
S
[music]
[музыка]
got
got
for its frightening and unusual ability
за устрашающий и необычную способность
this shark was nicknamed the goblin shark what
эту акулу прозвали акулой гоблином какую
ability this
способность вот эту
[music]
[музыка]
wawawawa
вававава
viene crer
viene crer
[music]
[музыка]
the probability that Muravye will start
вероятность того что Муравье начнёт
boarding your boat  Very small
брать твою лодку на абордаж Крайне мала
but never zero
но никогда не равна нулю
caralho B Liga Bora parar na beira
caralho B Liga Bora parar na beira
L muito Bravo
L muito Bravo
[music]
[музыка]
[applause]
[аплодисменты]
most often sand avalanches occur in
чаще всего песчаные лавины возникают в
dunes deserts or sand pits
дюнах пустынях или на песчаных карьерах
when wind water or external influences
когда ветер вода или внешнее воздействие
cause a mass of
приводит к сдвигу массы
sand to shift these guys were supposed to
песка эти ребята должны были здесь
fix something here but instead they started
что-то починить но вместо этого стали
drilling a pipe with water under the
сверлить трубу с водой под
result was not long in coming
результ не заставил себя долго ждать
He Semu
He Сему
[music]
[музыка]
[laughter]
[смех]
2011 a column of ash from the Japanese
2011 год столп пепла от японского
volcano Sim moe was so high
вулкана Сим мое был настолько высоким
that it reached the level of the clouds and began to
что достиг уровня облаков и стал
break through them
прорываться сквозь них
you
you
[music]
[музыка]
K
K
a [
а
music]
[музыка]
Go That's Way [music]
Go That's Way
workers were backing up but Even two pairs of
рабочие сдавали назад но Даже две пары
eyes couldn't help them notice the
глаз не помогли им заметить
parked car
припаркованную машину
[music]
[музыка]
such an unusual ritual for deer a way to
такой необычный обряд у оленей способ
protect themselves from predators in the center of this Circle
защиты от хищников в центре этого Круга
are the most vulnerable members of the herd
находятся самые уязвимые члены стада
cubs and  elderly individuals
детёныши и пожилые особи
[music]
[музыка]
oh
о
they were complete strangers but an
они были совершенно незнакомы но
aggressive dog unexpectedly made them
агрессивная собака неожиданно сделала их
neighbors in misfortune
соседями по несчастью
C
C
Oh my Oh My God
Oh my Oh My God
[music]
[музыка]
cats don't mix well with breakable
коты плохо сочетаются с бьющимся
objects have
предметами
you ever thought about what
ты когда-нибудь думал о том что делают
birds do during a hailstorm
птицы во время града
[music]
[музыка]
mov there She goes oh no there
mov there She
Go
no there Go
[music] the
[музыка]
unusual color of the soil of Armus Island in
необычный цвет почвы острова армус в
Iran makes rainy weather incredibly
Иране делает дождливую погоду невероятно
beautiful
красивой
[laughter]
[смех]
[music]
[музыка]
o W
о W
[laughter]
[смех]
ta They wanted to feed the animals but they were
та Они хотели покормить животных но были
n't ready for such closeness with them
не готовы к такой близости с ними
[applause]
[аплодисменты]
One
One
[music]
[музыка]
e
е
B
B
[music]
[музыка]
It seems that artificial intelligence is not the only one trying to take our jobs
похоже забрать у нас работу стремится не
What is this swimming style called
Как называется Этот стиль
SBA SBA
СБА СБА
come on bu come on come on come on no no no no
come on bu come on come on come on no no
She decided to do yoga here to
Она решила заняться йогой здесь чтобы
feel one with nature
почувствовать единство с природой
nature responded  reciprocity
природа ответила взаимностью
[music]
[музыка]
H
H
[laughter]
[смех]
[music]
[музыка]
quite significant that in a couple of years on a
довольно значительные то за пару лет на
motorcycle the mileage accumulates like an
мотоцикле набегает пробег как у
active taxi personally in 4 months I
активного такси лично за 4 месяца
drove more than 10,000 km
проехал более 10.000 км
A
A
J be careful oh so we drive in oxygen
J be careful ай так загоняем кислород
op it's getting
оп пошла
hot let the fish breathe a little
жара даём рыбе трох
ki
вздохнуть ки
sorogi I'm posting on it's all going away
сороги я поста на расходится всё
happyday Oh My
happyday Oh My
God Good Boy Oh My Go so I'm going to make horizontal cuts throughout The
God Good
onion That's Okay prob langsam G
onion That's Okay
ZU geben
prob langsam G ZU geben
[music] [
[музыка]
applause] [
[аплодисменты]
K a
K а
[music]
[музыка]
[applause]
[аплодисменты]